good morning everyone welcome to the
大家早上好，欢迎来到
last day of spring one or platform
春天的最后一天
spring one rotor it's nice to see that
弹簧一转，很高兴看到
there are so many people still awake and
仍然有很多人醒着
not totally crushed from the previous
不完全与以前
two days so thanks for showing up and
两天，感谢您的光临和
welcome to 40 tips and tricks for spring
欢迎使用40个春季提示和技巧
and IntelliJ IDEA
和IntelliJ IDEA
the title is a blatant lie because we
标题是公然的谎言，因为我们
show much more than 40 but I guess
显示超过40个，但我猜
you'll be fine with that
你会很好的
much less you only able to killed yeah
更何况你只能杀了
so my name is Yangtze blonde I am with
我叫长江金发女郎
the IntelliJ IDEA team and JetBrains I
IntelliJ IDEA团队和JetBrains I
work on the spring support and I'm very
在弹簧支架上工作，我非常
honored to have Stefan D coil from
荣幸地邀请Stefan D从
pivotal with me in the last defender I'm
我是最后一位防守者，对我至关重要
working on Spring Framework and spring
在Spring Framework和Spring上工作
boot and the reason I'm here is I'm
启动，我在这里的原因是我
actually working with yen on a daily
每天实际使用日元
basis on tooling support so we chat
基于工具支持，所以我们聊天
every now and then and we make sure that
时不时地，我们确保
the tooling support in IntelliJ IDEA for
IntelliJ IDEA中的工具支持
spring is excellent
春天很棒
yes so what is this talk about just to
是的，这是什么意思
give you a clearer idea what we are
让您更清楚地了解我们
going to do in the next hour this is the
接下来的一个小时要做的是
only slide you're going to see after
只是你要看的幻灯片
that I'm going to switch to IntelliJ and
我将要切换到IntelliJ
we will be doing a one-hour live coding
我们将进行一小时的现场编码
session we all try to cover as many sub
会议上，我们都试图涵盖尽可能多的子
projects and aspects of spring support
春季支持的项目和方面
in IntelliJ as possible in one hour and
一小时内在IntelliJ中
the key takeaway is today for you if you
如果您是今天，关键要点就是今天
are new to IntelliJ you're going to see
您将看到IntelliJ的新功能
what is actually possible with this
这实际上有什么可能
spring support if you already have some
春天的支持，如果你已经有一些
experience you hopefully pick up some
希望你有经验
new tips and tricks today learn about
今天有新的技巧和窍门
new stuff we put in the last version
我们在上一个版本中放的新内容
2016 . - which was released a couple of
2016。 -发行了
days ago so I guess we are ready to
天前，所以我想我们已经准备好
start but before that I have two
开始，但在那之前我有两个
questions who is using IntelliJ IDEA
谁在使用IntelliJ IDEA
already whoa-ho
已经哇！
80% okay so we have a lot of people with
80％好的，所以我们有很多人
at least some kind of experience who is
至少是某种经验
using Eclipse SDS or NetBeans okay just
使用Eclipse SDS或NetBeans可以
a few here we are not going to cover
这里有一些我们将不涉及
like the IDE basics today so if you
像今天的IDE基础知识一样，如果您
don't grab something please drop by
不要抓东西请顺路
later and
以后和
me why I do stuff like this and IntelliJ
我为什么要做这样的事情和IntelliJ
we just concentrate on the spring
我们只专注于春天
support today okay let's get started
今天就支持吧，让我们开始吧
so we have prepared a demonstration
所以我们准备了一个示范
project which is also available on
该项目也可以在
github I'm going to post the link later
github，我稍后再发布链接
on Twitter if you want to replay it at
在Twitter上，如果您想在
home to understand what we did today it
回家了解我们今天做了什么
also includes the script so you're
还包括脚本，所以您
really able to follow step by step what
真正能够循序渐进
we do today
我们今天做
so I just opened this demo project and
所以我刚刚打开了这个演示项目，
the first thing you notice in the lower
您在下部注意到的第一件事
right corner is this notification it's
右上角是这个通知
saying something that there are some and
说些什么
configured spring configuration files
配置的弹簧配置文件
found in this project so the basic idea
在这个项目中找到了基本的想法
in that Ellijay is if you want support
在那个埃利亚里，如果你想要支持
for a framework or library you need to
对于框架或库，您需要
add a so called facet a facet is
添加一个所谓的构面
basically meta information for that
基本上是元信息
framework which is added to the
框架已添加到
corresponding module and there you can
相应的模块，在那里
then enter specific settings for that
然后为此输入特定设置
technology framework whatever and it's
技术框架无论是什么
very important for an IntelliJ IDEA to
对于IntelliJ IDEA来说非常重要
actually know what your spring setup
真正知道你的弹簧设置
looks like and in some cases you have to
看起来像，在某些情况下，您必须
tell it what the context looks like so
告诉它上下文是什么样的
maybe Stefan can tell us a bit more
也许Stefan可以告诉我们更多
right so um really what's happening is
对，所以真的发生了什么
you have a bunch of configuration files
你有一堆配置文件
right so you define means you define
对，所以您定义意味着您定义
1000 drop again ok so what's really
再次下降1000，好吧
important is you need to make sure that
重要的是您需要确保
this spring facet is configure it in
这个弹簧面在配置它
IntelliJ IDE because it may not be such
IntelliJ IDE，因为可能不是这样
obvious now they've improved that a lot
现在很明显，他们已经改善了很多
with this notification but you may be in
收到此通知，但您可能在
a situation where you think the spring
你认为春天的情况
support is enabled and it's really not
支持已启用，实际上不是
really enabled because as as long as you
真正启用，因为只要你
don't create this facet with the context
不要用上下文创建这个方面
IntelliJ IDEA cannot pass your
IntelliJ IDEA无法通过您的
configuration and give you smart
配置，给你聪明
auto-completion so one way to know about
自动补全是了解的一种方式
that stuff is when when you when you
那东西是当你当你
when you are in a component and a class
当您在组件和类中时
so you open any bin that you have you
所以你打开任何你拥有的垃圾箱
have an add component on it if you don't
如果没有的话，上面有一个添加组件
have a gutter icon on the Left it means
左侧有一个装订线图标
that IntelliJ IDEA does not know it's a
IntelliJ IDEA不知道这是一个
spring beam and if it does not know it's
弹簧梁，如果它不知道它是
it's a spring beam then it can give you
这是弹簧梁，它可以给你
a completion down the road so the the
未来的完成，所以
most important part I think in the
我认为最重要的部分
presentation is make sure that the
演示文稿要确保
spring facet is configured for your
弹簧面已为您配置
module properly and we're going to show
模块正确，我们将展示
you how to do this
你怎么做
right so there are a couple of links in
对，所以有几个链接
this notification yeah I'm going to
这个通知是的，我要去
switch to the presentation mode in a
切换到演示模式
minute just one league which is called
分钟只有一个联赛，这叫做
create default context what that does is
创建默认上下文的作用是
you can organize your spring context and
您可以组织春季背景，
or you can organize your spring
或者你可以组织你的春天
configuration files in various contexts
各种上下文中的配置文件
so they are really separate and they're
所以他们真的是分开的，他们是
right you can model like hierarchies in
对，您可以在其中像层次结构一样建模
your context use a parent relationship
您的上下文使用父母关系
between two contacts which is by the way
顺便说一下，两个联系人之间
the default setup for Spring NBC you
Spring NBC的默认设置
have servlet context and an application
有servlet上下文和一个应用程序
context and they have dependencies
上下文，它们具有依赖性
between each era so what does this
在每个时代之间，这是什么
create default context fix do for us it
创建默认的上下文修复程序为我们做
will create that spring facet and it
将创建那个春天的方面，它
will also put all the phone
也会把所有的电话
configuration files into one global file
配置文件合并为一个全局文件
set which is in most cases what most
设置在大多数情况下是什么
applications can work with then you can
应用程序可以与您一起工作
still tweak it or set it up manually
仍然对其进行调整或手动设置
later there is though a very important
后来，尽管有一个非常重要的
thing with spring boot and spring MVC
Spring Boot和Spring MVC的事情
you don't need and you shouldn't try to
你不需要，你不应该尝试
configure those applications manually in
在以下位置手动配置这些应用程序
the spring facet because those
春天的方面，因为那些
applications has very strict rules on
应用程序具有非常严格的规则
how they are set up so we run an auto
如何设置它们，以便我们运行自动
detection on them and we create the
检测它们，我们创建
necessary files for you automatically
自动为您准备必要的文件
and you cannot edit them and you
而且您无法编辑它们，而您
shouldn't try to do it manually so the
不应该尝试手动进行操作，因此
bottom line is if you using spring boot
最重要的是如果您使用的是弹簧靴
or spring MVC they'll take care of you
或春季MVC，他们会照顾您
yeah so I get a notification on the top
是的，所以我会在顶部收到通知
that it already found some order
已经找到订单了
detected context for spring MVC because
检测到Spring MVC的上下文，因为
that's part of the demonstration and it
那是示范的一部分
notifies me that I can now perform the
通知我现在可以执行
setup for any additional configuration
设置任何其他配置
files because it doesn't know if I need
文件，因为它不知道我是否需要
or how many contacts are need and what
或需要多少联系以及什么
files should be in what context so
文件应该在什么环境下
that's something the user has to do
这是用户必须要做的
later I'm just going to close the
稍后我将要关闭
quantification for now and we are now
现在量化，我们现在
going
去
and to code mode so what we have here is
和编码模式，所以我们这里是
a very simple configuration class and it
一个非常简单的配置类，它
has some yellow highlighting and the
有一些黄色突出显示，并且
warning is that the application context
警告是应用程序上下文
is not configured because as I said we
没有配置，因为正如我所说，
need to set up those five sets we
需要设置这五组
already have a spring facet which was
已经有一个弹簧面
created by the quick fix I just invoked
由我刚刚调用的快速修复程序创建
and I can now press alt enter to invoke
现在我可以按alt enter来调用
the quick fix menu from IntelliJ IDEA
IntelliJ IDEA的快速修复菜单
this is really one of the most important
这真的是最重要的之一
shortcuts in IntelliJ by the way all the
IntelliJ中的所有快捷方式
shortcuts are shown on the bottom of the
快捷方式显示在
screen they may differ on your system on
屏幕上它们可能在您的系统上有所不同
or depending on the key map it shows but
或取决于它显示的按键图，但是
it's one of the key things to do if you
这是您要做的关键事情之一
want to master an IDE learn the
想精通IDE学习
shortcuts because otherwise you are
快捷方式，因为否则
wasting your time
浪费你的时间
so let's invoke this prefix I can create
所以让我们调用这个我可以创建的前缀
now a new context and this will open the
现在一个新的背景，这将打开
configuration dialog I can give it a
配置对话框，我可以给它一个
descriptive name and then the
描述性名称，然后
configuration class which I used to
我曾经使用过的配置类
invoke this fix already pre-selected I'm
调用已经预先选择的此修复程序
just going for that single convict class
只是去那个有罪的班
click OK and if you just noticed on the
单击确定，如果您刚刚在
left side of the editor that's the
编辑器的左侧是
so-called gutter area where we show
我们展示的所谓的排水沟区域
icons which are mostly for information
主要用于提供信息的图标
or navigation purposes and we just
或导航目的，我们只是
received a bunch of them so that means
收到了一堆，这意味着
now the warning has also gone away so
现在警告也消失了，所以
the IntelliJ IDE now understands that
IntelliJ IDE现在可以理解
this configuration is part of your
此配置是您的一部分
spring setup in your project so in the
在您的项目中设置弹簧，因此在
demonstration we'll create several
演示，我们将创建几个
context with only a subset of your
仅包含您的一个子集的上下文
configuration in the project the reason
在项目中配置的原因
why we will do that is to just separate
我们为什么要做的就是分开
them as a separate example so that they
他们作为一个单独的例子，以便他们
don't pull you to each other
不要拉你彼此
but in practice in your own project
但实际上是在您自己的项目中
usually what you have is one facet with
通常你拥有的只是一个方面
one context and you configured it right
一个上下文，并且您对其进行了正确配置
so don't get confused if we start
所以开始就不要困惑
creating a bunch of contacts this is not
创建一堆联系人，这不是
something you
你的东西
you you will do in a regular project all
您将在一个常规项目中全部完成
right let's take a look at those icons
正确，让我们看一下那些图标
so the first one I want to talk about is
所以我要谈的第一个是
this year and the food tip says
今年，食物提示说
something about spring model
关于弹簧模型
dependencies so this configuration class
依赖项，因此此配置类
does have a couple of additional spring
确实有几个额外的弹簧
config related annotations we have a
与配置相关的注释，我们有一个
component scan we have an import for
组件扫描，我们有一个导入
additional configuration classes and we
其他配置类，我们
also import some pics and every source
还导入一些图片和每个来源
just to go back a bit to the 90s and
只是要回到90年代
sometimes it's a bit hard to understand
有时候有点难以理解
what the actual context at runtime will
运行时的实际上下文是什么
look like when you have imports when you
看起来像当您进口时
have component scans you could possibly
进行组件扫描
create a huge set of configuration
创建大量的配置
classes which are dependent on that main
依赖于该主类的类
configuration class and we can inspect
配置类，我们可以检查
this right in the IDE by just clicking
在IDE中只需单击即可
on this show model dependencies diagram
在此显示模型依赖关系图
and we can see that there are a couple
我们可以看到有几个
of nodes here which which represent on
这里代表的节点数
this level the files at the context we
这个级别的文件在上下文中我们
have then the configuration class which
然后有配置类
is defined it also shows a bit more
定义它也显示更多
information in the tooltip like the
工具提示中的信息，例如
number of imports and stuff like that
进口数量和类似的东西
and then we can see all those imports
然后我们可以看到所有这些进口
which we just discussed an import can
我们刚刚讨论了导入可以
have other imports so you can actually
还有其他进口，所以你实际上可以
see the whole graph of your
看到你的整个图
configuration as it will be built by
配置，因为它将由
spring at runtime and this is a very
春天在运行时，这是一个非常
nice feature I think to understand setup
我想了解设置的不错功能
project set up problems in your project
项目中存在项目中的问题
if you are new to a project and if you
如果您是项目的新手，如果您
need to understand what the structure of
需要了解什么结构
the spring configuration actually does
弹簧配置实际上可以
at runtime of course we can navigate
当然在运行时我们可以导航
from here to the corresponding nodes so
从这里到对应的节点
that's what I'm going to do in this XML
这就是我要在此XML中执行的操作
file which is included on our second
第二个文件
level
水平
this graph is also very nice to detect
这个图也很好检测
cycles so for demonstration purposes I
为了演示的目的，我
duplicated this component scan
复制了此组件扫描
definition which will result and all the
将导致的定义以及所有
beans or configuration classes which are
bean或配置类是
scanned being duplicated is that
扫描被复制的是
something that happens quite often or
经常发生的事情或
yeah well depends on your project really
是的，这取决于您的项目
if you typically if you use a spring
如果您通常使用弹簧
good application with the directory
与目录良好的应用程序
structure that we recommend you have
我们建议您使用的结构
less chances to end up in that situation
出现这种情况的机会更少
but if you have a project a spring
但是如果你有一个春天的项目
framework based project with lots of
基于框架的项目有很多
instrument configuration it's not really
仪器配置不是真的
easy to figure out what's coming and one
容易弄清楚会发生什么，一个
so typically for four cycles the the
因此通常四个周期
context actually is quite powerful to
上下文实际上对
detect them and to still be able to load
检测到它们并仍然能够加载
your application which I think can be a
您认为我的申请可以
problem right because we've built that
对的问题，因为我们已经建立了
feature the community ask us to be
社区要求我们成为
smarter about it but on the other hand
关于它更聪明，但另一方面
the fact that you don't have an
你没有一个事实
exception right away means also that
立即例外也意味着
sometimes you your configuration is
有时您的配置是
actually invalid and you don't really
实际上是无效的，而你不是真的
know it's invalid one thing which can be
知道这是无效的一件事
a problem in this situation is if you if
在这种情况下的问题是
you scan a beam definition that doesn't
您扫描的光束定义不
have an ID so if you think about the XML
有一个ID，所以如果您考虑XML
configuration being class some class
配置是某类
right you don't specify an ID because
对，您不指定ID，因为
you don't need that if you import that
如果导入，则不需要
class twice you'll get two bin
两次上课，你会得到两个垃圾箱
definitions for that thing because the
那个东西的定义，因为
first time it's going to be processed
第一次要处理
the bin definition will be read an
箱定义将被读取
automatic an automated generated ID will
自动生成一个自动生成的ID
be associated to it and the second time
关联到第二次
we'll process it
我们会处理
well we'll pass it again and generate
好吧，我们将再次传递它并生成
another automated generated ID for that
另一个为此自动生成的ID
so you'll end up with two bins in the
所以你最终会在两个垃圾箱里
contacts and you probably don't want
联系人，您可能不想要
that right so I've seen a lot of people
没错，所以我见过很多人
actually fixing that by adding an ID
通过添加ID来实际解决此问题
because in this case since you provide
因为在这种情况下，因为您提供
the idea and the idea the same the bin
这个想法和这个想法一样
definition will be overridden and you'll
定义将被覆盖，您将
end up with one bin but really what you
最终只有一个垃圾箱，但实际上你
should do is use those kinds of features
应该做的就是使用这些功能
to detect those cycles and cut those
找出那些周期并削减那些
cycles so maybe it's a bit hard to see
周期，所以也许很难看到
on the screen but there is a red
在屏幕上，但是有一个红色
arrow here duplicating basically the
这里的箭头基本上重复了
blue arrow which defines the original
定义原始文字的蓝色箭头
and not duplicated components can and
并且没有重复的组件可以并且
again I can even click on those errors
我什至可以点击那些错误
and it will bring me to the exact
它会带我确切
definition where this note is referenced
引用此注释的定义
from so that's a really nice feature to
从这是一个非常好的功能
spot set up problems and visualize
发现问题并可视化
setups of your spring app if you're
如果您是Spring应用程序的设置
using Java confit you've noticed that in
使用Java confit，您已经注意到
the components can annotation there is a
组件可以注释有一个
getter icon next to it there's actually
旁边的吸气剂图标实际上是
of one of the one of my most favorite
我最喜欢的人之一
feature if you click on that you'll
功能，如果您单击它，您将
basically get the list of beans that
基本上得到的豆列表
have been imported that have been found
已导入已发现的
via that's direct that directive so you
通过那是直接的指令，所以你
may have several components can for
可能有几个组件可以
whatever reason probably don't do that
不管什么原因可能都不这样做
but unite with different package days
但要配合不同的打包日
and if you click on each individual ones
如果您单击每个单独的
you'll exactly see the beans that will
您会确切地看到可以
be registered at one time it's very
一次注册非常
useful right
有用的权利
so we see the list of B names and
所以我们看到了B名称列表和
classes or types of those beans and we
这些豆子的类别或类型，我们
can of course click on them to navigate
当然可以点击它们进行导航
to the beans which are actually included
到实际包含的豆子中
by the components can definition but one
由组件可以定义，但一个
of my favorite tricks to save time in
我最喜欢的技巧以节省时间
any or most of all these pop-up or
这些弹出窗口中的任何一个或大多数
completion lists and IntelliJ is to use
完成列表，并使用IntelliJ
a feature which is called click
一种称为点击的功能
definition when I do that it will
当我这样做的时候定义
actually open this pore up here and show
实际上在这里打开毛孔并显示
me an inline editor representation of
我是的内联编辑器表示形式
that navigation target so I don't have
该导航目标，所以我没有
to click on it to see what is actually
单击它以查看实际上是什么
behind this name but I can just see it
这个名字的后面，但我只能看到它
in the list I can open the other one as
在列表中，我可以打开另一个
well and I don't have to leave my
好吧，我不必离开我的
current editor just to inspect stuff
目前的编辑只是为了检查东西
so in Spring Framework there is this
所以在Spring Framework中有这个
this feature that that's quite popular
这个很流行的功能
these days it which is MIT annotations
这些天是MIT注释
we we've used that extensively in the
我们已经在
framework these days
这些天的框架
so metal notation is about composing
所以金属符号是关于组成
seven annotations for a given use case
给定用例的七个注释
so in Spring Framework for the three we
所以在Spring框架中，我们三个
have this get mapping annotation you all
所有人都有这个获取映射注释
probably know if you use spring MVC
大概知道您是否使用spring MVC
request mapping where you basically give
请求映射，你基本上给
the path and some attributes such as the
路径和一些属性，例如
HTTP method to bind to so if you need to
要绑定的HTTP方法，因此如果需要
if you need to have a request mapping on
如果您需要一个请求映射
the same URI for post and yet you'll
用于发布的相同URI，但您会
have two methods one that says okay I
有两种方法，一种说我可以
want four to get and I want for the post
想要四个得到，我想要这个职位
so we thought that maybe it would be
所以我们认为也许
nice to have some kind of dedicated
很高兴有一些奉献精神
annotation for that and yet still
为此的注释，但仍然
support all the features so we in photo
支持所有功能，因此我们在照片中
3 we have get mapping and post mapping
3我们有映射和后映射
which is basically a meta annotation on
这基本上是一个元注释
request mapping with the dedicated
用专用请求映射
method so don't you don't have to
方法，所以你不必
specify you can do that for plenty of
指定您可以做到这一点
things so for instance if you have a
例如，如果您有一个
service that needs to enable cache and
需要启用缓存和
transaction and you could create an
交易，您可以创建一个
annotation my transactional cat or
注释我的交易猫或
whatever the name it is my service that
不管名字是我的服务
will apply those two aspects what's
将应用这两个方面是什么
important effectively is when you do
重要的是当你做
that or when you use such feature you
或当您使用此类功能时
don't lose ID inspection so again is
不要丢失身份证检查，所以再次
going to show you now what happens if
现在要告诉你如果
you create your own components can
您创建自己的组件可以
annotation again it's not something you
再次注释不是你
would do it's demo purposes but keep in
会达到演示目的，但要保持
mind that that's the kind of feature you
请注意，这就是您的功能
would expect if you meet annotate other
会期望如果您遇到其他注释
features right so text let's take a very
正确的功能，让文字让我们
quick look into our demonstration
快速查看我们的示范
annotation as you can see we have the
如您所见，我们有
add component scan here so it's
在此处添加组件扫描
recognized as a meta annotation of the
被识别为
Spring Framework or annotation and
Spring框架或注释和
there's a dedicated annotation to also
有专门的注释
redefine existing attributes so you can
重新定义现有属性，以便您可以
read eclair and give them a new name and
阅读eclair并给他们起一个新名字，
this allows for annotation also receives
这允许注释也接收
code completion support and IntelliJ so
代码完成支持和IntelliJ这样
what I have here I have a string array
我在这里有一个字符串数组
which should redefine the original base
应该重新定义原始基础
packages attribute
包属性
and IntelliJ IDEA will automatically
和IntelliJ IDEA将自动
show me all matching attributes which
显示所有匹配的属性
are available in the original components
在原始组件中可用
can annotation and propose those names
可以注释并建议这些名称
for me because I also defined from what
对我来说，因为我也从什么定义
annotation I want to Allies existing
我想让同盟存在的注释
attributes form and going back to the
属性表格，然后回到
main configuration you can see that all
主要配置，您可以看到所有
the navigation icons and stuff are still
导航图标和东西仍然
available and that works basically for
可用，并且基本上适用于
all your own custom meta annotation so
所有您自己的自定义元注释
anytime you do something like this you
每当你做这样的事情
will not lose the IDE support which is
不会失去对IDE的支持
built for the original Spring Framework
为原始的Spring框架构建
annotation but it will be smart enough
注解，但足够聪明
to figure out that you actually are
弄清楚你实际上是
using the original attribute and provide
使用原始属性并提供
the same level of support for that as
对此的支持程度与
well so if you feel that there's too
好吧，如果您觉得还有
many getter icons on the left and you
左侧有许多吸气剂图标，您
start to be a bit sick of it because
开始有点厌烦，因为
maybe some of them are not really useful
也许其中一些并不是真的有用
keep in mind that you can actually
请记住，您实际上可以
disable them if you don't want to see
如果您不想看到，请禁用它们
for instance your diagram thing because
例如你的图表的东西，因为
you're not using it very often it's very
您不会经常使用它
easy to disable that in the options yeah
容易在选项中禁用它
so we try to split up all the gutter
所以我们尝试把所有的水槽分开
icons into a separate setting so you can
图标设置为单独的设置，以便您可以
really tune it according to your
根据您的情况进行调整
personal preference okay so much first
个人喜好首先
from now on the code configuration stuff
从现在开始代码配置
we are going to come back to this class
我们将回到这个班级
in a minute but first we are going to
等一下，但是首先我们要
switch to something about the UI so
切换到有关UI的内容
there is a dedicated spring tool window
有一个专用的弹簧工具窗口
in IntelliJ IDEA what can I do here I
在IntelliJ IDEA中我可以在这里做什么
can see the list of beans in my project
可以看到我项目中的bean列表
which is very handy because you can
这非常方便，因为您可以
actually make sure that your setup is
实际确保您的设置是
correct by just checking for the
只需检查
resulting beans which hopefully matches
产生的豆有望匹配
what you would want at one time and you
您一次想要什么，您
can also use it to show more information
也可以用它显示更多信息
about it so when I click here it
关于它，所以当我单击此处
click accidentially so it already opened
意外点击，因此它已经打开
the definition of that beam but you also
光束的定义，但你也
have documentation support here we can
在这里有文档支持，我们可以
see that some of those beans are
看到其中一些豆子是
highlighted with a different background
用不同的背景突出显示
color that is because they are implicit
颜色是因为它们是隐式的
beans which are provided by the spring
春天提供的豆子
framework automatically we can switch
框架自动我们可以切换
them on and off if we don't want to see
如果我们不想看到它们的话
them and you can also see some
他们，你也可以看到一些
infrastructure beans like key components
基础架构豆（如关键组件）
game stuff another thing which is very
游戏的东西另一件事是非常
nice when I close this tool window for
当我关闭此工具窗口时
now and I go back to one of my beans in
现在，我回到我的一个豆子里
my application sometimes it's a bit hard
我的应用有时会有点困难
to understand where it is actually
了解它的实际位置
defined so one thing I need to enable
定义，所以我需要启用一件事
first to make it more useful is to show
首先使其更有用的是展示
the contexts as well and you can see we
以及上下文，您可以看到我们
have two hierarchy between the context
在上下文之间有两个层次
to configuration files and then the
配置文件，然后
resulting beans ok
由此产生的豆还可以
closing that again and when your cursor
当您的光标再次关闭
is on some definition there's a generic
在某种定义上有一个通用的
feature in IntelliJ to navigate or
IntelliJ中的功能来导航或
select that element in one of the tool
在工具之一中选择该元素
windows and that's called select in just
Windows，这就是所谓的选择
a couple of navigation targets the
几个导航目标
project view for example but also the
例如项目视图
spring beans use so when I select that
春季豆使用，所以当我选择
one it will actually expand the tree
一种实际上会扩展树
automatically to match the corresponding
自动匹配相应的
configuration and the contexts which are
配置和上下文是
responsible for setting up that bean so
负责设置那个bean，所以
that's a nice way to inspect where does
这是检查在哪里做的好方法
this bean come from where did I set it
这个豆是从哪里来的
up ok ok so much about the spring tool
好，好，关于弹簧工具
window at CSUN code yes that's actually
CSUN代码的窗口，是的，实际上
type a bit now so back to our main
现在输入一点，回到我们的主
configuration class first thing we are
配置类我们第一件事
going to do is we are a bit unsure what
我们要做的是有点不确定
may be the screen top bar here is it
可能是屏幕顶部栏
doesn't really show any text but the
并未真正显示任何文字，但
tooltip says something about active
工具提示说了一些关于主动
profiles so what our profile spring
轮廓，所以我们的轮廓弹簧
right so profile is a spring feature
对，所以轮廓是弹簧的特征
that allows you to tune the context for
允许您调整上下文
instance to override some beans or to
实例来覆盖一些bean或
add additional beans or in the case of
添加其他豆类，或者
spring boot add additional configuration
弹簧靴添加其他配置
right so the most basic example you
对，所以最基本的例子
could find if you're using Spring
可以找到您是否正在使用Spring
Framework Directive you probably create
您可能创建的框架指令
the datasource
数据源
yourself which you wouldn't do if you if
你自己，如果你不愿意的话
you were using spring good and in the
你用的是春天的好东西
local environment you want to have a in
您想进入的本地环境
memory database and when you deploy your
内存数据库以及部署时
app in production you want to use iron
您想使用铁的生产中的应用程序
or some person database whatever you
或某人的数据库
choose to use so there's really two bin
选择使用，所以实际上有两个垃圾箱
definitions or maybe some properties
定义或某些属性
that I've changed that are changing and
我已经改变了，正在改变，
you want to be able to do that without
你想能够做到这一点而没有
changing the content of the jar so you
改变罐子里的东西，让你
want to have the same application and
希望拥有相同的应用程序，并且
just flip a switch and enable one or the
只需拨动开关并启用一个或
other
其他
Spring Framework has this profile
Spring Framework具有此配置文件
annotation you can use on configuration
您可以在配置上使用的注释
classes to say enable that configuration
可以启用该配置的类
class when the want that profile is
想要该个人资料时上课
active right so you could say you could
积极的权利，所以你可以说你可以
put the production database in some kind
将生产数据库放入某种形式
of production database configure
生产数据库配置
whatever add profile production on top
在顶部添加任何配置文件生产
and every beans that are that are
还有那些
defined there will be loaded and will
定义那里将被加载并将
eventually override the ones which have
最终超越那些
no profile and there is a way to enable
没有个人资料，有一种方法可以启用
profile by a property but right here
按属性进行配置，但就在这里
what we have is we would maybe we can
我们拥有的是我们也许可以
activate a profile something that's what
激活个人资料
you want to do so yeah so we can
你想这样做，所以我们可以
actually simulate that switching that
实际模拟切换
Stefan just explained for example
斯蒂芬举例说明
between death and production environment
在死亡和生产环境之间
by telling the IDE which profile should
通过告诉IDE应该使用哪个配置文件
be active right now in my IDE so that I
立即在我的IDE中处于活动状态，以便我
can navigate the spring context as if it
可以像浏览弹簧上下文一样导航
were on the set environment for example
例如在设定的环境中
so that's really the second step right
所以这实际上是第二步
the first step is to configure the
第一步是配置
current text if you're using spring boot
当前文本（如果您使用的是Spring Boot）
spring MVC that's done automatically for
Spring MVC自动完成
you so that IntelliJ IDEA knows about
您，以便IntelliJ IDEA知道
the country right it knows about what
它知道什么的国家
you've defined the second step is to say
您已经定义了第二步是说
in my environment right now I'm running
现在在我的环境中
with the production profile so what that
与生产资料有关
means is whenever you ask for the data
意思是每当您要求数据时
source B it's going to point to the beam
源B将指向光束
definition that actually defines the
实际上定义了
production data source because it will
生产数据源，因为它将
know because you said I'm running with
知道，因为你说我正在与
with the production profile so it
与生产资料一样
doesn't do anything special at runtime
在运行时没有做任何特别的事情
but it gives you inspection like the
但是它给你像
profile was active so here we can change
个人资料处于活动状态，因此我们可以在此处进行更改
the active profile actually on different
活动配置文件实际上在不同的位置
levels on project level on module level
项目级别在模块级别
or even on the specific context we have
甚至在特定情况下
two profiles here main and custom I'm
这里有两个配置文件，主要和自定义
going to activate the main profile now
现在要激活主配置文件
we can see the name of the active
我们可以看到活动名称
profile is now shown in the editor top
配置文件现在显示在编辑器顶部
bar so you are always aware what profile
栏，因此您始终知道什么配置文件
did I just activate in my IDE what am I
我刚刚在IDE中激活了我是什么吗
seeing right now are those arrows
现在看到的是那些箭头
actually what I want to see right now
我现在想看的东西
but there is a red thing on the yellow
但是黄色有红色的东西
mean yes I'm sorry
是的，对不起
haha that's on purpose I'm sure so
哈哈那是故意的
there's a long beam please excuse the
有长光束请原谅
type it's just for demonstration
输入只是用于演示
purposes but there are apparently two
目的，但显然有两个
beans defined which would match by the
定义的将与
type long and say swing doesn't know
长按并说挥杆不知道
what to do right right so if you if you
该怎么做才对，所以如果你
start this app it will fail and IntelliJ
启动此应用程序将失败，并IntelliJ
IDEA knows right now already that it
IDEA现在已经知道了
will fail because of the profile you've
由于您的个人资料而失败
enabled there is probably our next trap
启用可能是我们的下一个陷阱
in the finish
在最后
for that bean type that has been added
对于已添加的那个bean类型
or something and you know you're
或类似的东西，你知道你是
basically asking the contacts give me a
基本上问联系人给我一个
bean of that type but there's two of
那种豆，但是有两个
them and you're not specifying which one
他们，你没有指定哪一个
spring should actually inject so what's
春天实际上应该注入，那是什么
nice is that IntelliJ IDEA knows about
很高兴IntelliJ IDEA知道
that stuff and it it will be able to
那东西，它将能够
warn you and to give you a system so
警告您并给您系统
maybe we could try a quick fix and see
也许我们可以尝试快速修复并看看
what happens
怎么了
maybe there's a quick fix hooray - whoa
也许有一个快速修复万岁-哇
so it's the same shortcut again remember
所以这是同样的捷径
main configuration with it quick fix add
快速修复添加的主要配置
to the facet it's always the same
从各个方面来看，它始终是相同的
shortcut so whenever you see a warning
快捷方式，以便每当您看到警告时
whenever you see a one in bit in the
每当你看到一个
spring support or not always use that
弹簧支撑或不总是使用
quick fix because probably do the first
快速修复，因为可能第一个
option will be some something to help
选项会有所帮助
you fix that so the quick fix it shows
您修复了它，因此它显示了快速修复
me here are two actually on the first
我这里实际上是两个
upper ones the first one is to add in
较高的第一个是添加
qualifier which we are going to do in a
我们将在
second and the second one is also
第二和第二个也是
interesting because I can actually no
有趣，因为我实际上没有
show again the list of beans which are
再次显示豆的列表
possible auto wiring cat need candidates
可能需要自动布线的猫需要候选人
in that place and again I can use my
在那个地方，我可以再次使用我的
favorite shortcut trick definition to
最喜欢的快捷方式技巧定义为
inspect them to see which one do I
检查他们，看看我该选择哪一个
actually want so when I now invoke the
当我现在调用
fix to add the qualifying qualifier
修复添加合格的限定词
annotation of course again you get auto
当然，您再次获得注解
completion here and I can just pick one
完成这里，我可以选择一个
I can control click here
我可以控制点击这里
I even have clicked up here right and
我什至在这里点击了
the editor I can go there and we can see
编辑我可以去那里，我们可以看到
yes this is correct because this
是的，这是正确的，因为这
configuration is active for main profile
主配置文件的配置已激活
only and IntelliJ IDEA understands all
仅IntelliJ IDEA了解所有内容
of this in your IDE right so that's a
在您的IDE中正确执行此操作
huge time-saver if you use profiles or
如果您使用配置文件或
auto wiring or any of those features
自动接线或任何这些功能
that you get validation immediately as
您立即获得验证
you set up your application while
您在设置应用程序的同时
writing the code so I think that still
编写代码，所以我认为仍然
may be a problem here
可能是个问题
that idea always complaining really
这个想法总是在抱怨
singing oh the autopilot annotation
唱歌哦，自动驾驶仪注释
doesn't like it
不喜欢
fuel injection is not recommended why's
不推荐燃油喷射，为什么
that so you probably heard of that
所以你可能听说过
before
之前
the spring team recommends you not use
春季团队建议您不要使用
feeling ejection for one it does not
感觉到它不会弹出
enforce unit ability of your service so
加强服务的单位能力，因此
if you inject dependencies there's no
如果注入依赖项，则没有
reason to change them so you probably
更改它们的原因，所以您可能
want to make the fields final and you
想要使字段最终确定，而您
can't do that second is if you use that
第二个是做不到的
technique you can't use the field in the
技术，您不能使用
constructor because we first need to
构造函数，因为我们首先需要
create an instance and once we have the
创建一个实例，一旦我们有了
instance we can set the value on the
实例，我们可以在
field that's what auto I already on the
这就是我已经在
field does so if you start to use that
如果您开始使用该字段，则这样做
field which usually you should without
通常你应该没有的领域
to bring framework then you'll get a new
带来框架，那么你会得到一个新的
printer exception because the field is
打印机异常，因为该字段是
not set yet and lastly if you promote
尚未设定，最后如果您提升
constructor injection it's much more
构造函数注入
easier to test your code without spring
更轻松地测试代码
which is something you should do
这是你应该做的
whenever possible yeah and was one blog
是的，只要是一个博客
post which was quite popular with us and
该帖子在我们中很受欢迎
it was written by Oliver guca from
它是由Oliver guca撰写的
spring Gator team and he made a nice
春天的鳄鱼队，他表现不错
round not to use field injection ever so
尽量不要使用场注入
so if you use if you upgrade IntelliJ
所以如果您使用如果您升级IntelliJ
IDE and you use fear injection and
IDE，您使用恐惧注入和
you'll get that background by default
您将默认获得该背景
yeah that picture automatically pops up
是的，图片会自动弹出
in your editor
在您的编辑器中
kudos to Oliver for making us aware of
感谢奥利弗（Oliver）使我们意识到
this really bad way of doing auto wiring
这种自动接线的糟糕方法
and so there's a quick fix right yeah of
因此，有一个快速修复方法，对
course this is a quick fix so again
当然，这是一个快速修复
hitting all enter show intention actions
点击全部进入显示意图动作
and I can convert this node to the
我可以将此节点转换为
recommended way which is to use
推荐的使用方式
constructor injection that's it no
构造函数注入就是这样
manual typing one prefix you're done
手动输入一个完成的前缀
okay right so the question is do you
好吧，所以问题是
still get a quick fix if there is
如果有的话仍然可以快速解决
already a constructor I'm pretty sure it
我已经很确定了
does that yeah so it creates a new
是的，所以它创建了一个新的
constructor just with the 24 at any
构造函数仅需24
additional criteria there's not this
其他标准不是
year
年
so it also put the qualifier annotation
所以它也放了限定词注解
there so we are good to go right
在那里，所以我们很高兴向右走
actually I want to see what happens when
其实我想看看什么时候发生
I change the profile so I can invoke
我更改了个人资料，因此可以调用
that action also by a go to action which
该行动还可以通过采取行动来实现
is your one stop shortcut find action
是您的一站式快捷查找操作
just start typing the action name and it
刚开始输入动作名称和它
will show you our matching actions and
将向您展示我们的匹配操作，并
one of them is change active spring
其中之一是改变活跃的春天
profiles we get the same menu I invoked
配置文件，我们得到与我调用的菜单相同的菜单
from the top navigation bar before I'm
从顶部导航栏开始
going to switch to the custom profile
切换到自定义配置文件
now to see what happens here
现在看看这里发生了什么
oops so the long bean one ID is not
哎呀，所以长豆一个ID不是
available in the custom profile so we
在自定义配置文件中可用，因此我们
need to fix that and again I press
需要解决这个问题，然后再按一次
control space to invoke completion and
控制空间以调用完成和
now it shows me the beans which are
现在它向我展示了
available in the other profile which I
我可以在其他个人资料中找到
just selected right so that's all we
刚刚选择正确，仅此而已
have to say about auto wiring and
必须说一下自动接线和
profiles but I think it's a real nice
个人资料，但我认为这真的很不错
feature to avoid setup errors and be
功能避免设置错误并成为
sure that your application actually
确保您的应用程序实际上
starts starts up okay
启动就可以了
I'm happy that we only have 25 minutes
很高兴我们只有25分钟
left because we're able to skip the
离开是因为我们能够跳过
excellent section yes
优秀的部分是
so XML fans and so we are going to skip
XML爱好者，所以我们将跳过
that section at a part of the session
该部分在会议的一部分
unless you disagree right should we skip
除非您不同意，否则我们应该跳过
the XML support or a thumbs up so we'll
XML支持或建议，所以我们将
skip that someone will not happy I know
跳过，有人会不高兴，我知道
but okay next topic spring caching what
但是好吧，下一个主题春季缓存什么
is spring passion so you've seen that at
是春天的激情，所以你已经看到了
the keynote right so you annotate your
正确的主题演讲，以便您注释您的
method with the the cache annotation and
带有缓存注释的方法和
we will add a cache aspect to it
我们将为其添加缓存方面
whenever you invoke the method sorry
每当您调用方法对不起
we'll check if there is an entry in a
我们将检查是否有一个条目
cache so you need to specify a name or
缓存，因此您需要指定一个名称或
multiple names and if there is none what
多个名称，如果没有名称
will invoke your method as usual and
将照常调用您的方法，
update the cache economy if there is we
如果有的话，更新缓存的经济性
won't even invoke your method and we'll
甚至不会调用您的方法，我们会
return the information directly
直接返回信息
so what Yun is showing now is a same
所以允云现在显示的是一样的
thing with filled injection you can see
充满注射的东西，你可以看到
that the cache annotation is on the
缓存注释在
interface and there is a warning about
界面，并且有关于
that the reason why there is a warning
出现警告的原因
about that is because it's an
关于那是因为这是一个
implementation detail right so you may
正确的实施细节，因此您可以
decide that one implementation use
决定使用一种实现
caching and another one doesn't you may
缓存，另一个可能不是
disagree with that fact so whenever
不同意这个事实，所以无论何时
there is those warnings you can easily
有那些警告，您可以轻松地
disable that in the IDE if you disagree
如果您不同意，请在IDE中将其禁用
with them but I think also it's nice
和他们在一起，但我认为这也很好
that the spring team and the JetBrains
春季团队和JetBrains
team they work together to actually push
他们共同努力的团队
some of these best practices to you that
其中一些最佳实践
you get a chance to well know about that
您有机会充分了解这一点
stuff okay so I am following the
好的，所以我正在关注
recommended way others abling this
推荐其他人使用的方法
annotation on the interface level going
接口级别的注解
to the actual implementation and
到实际实施
enabling it here on the implementation
在实施中启用它
and there's a null warning it wants
它想要一个空警告
something like
就像是
Krishna in waters first so the that's
克里希纳首先在水域中，所以那是
really a nice story about that stuff in
关于那个东西的故事真的很好
three two and wind should use the
三二和风应使用
caching infrastructure the way you
以您的方式缓存基础架构
specify the cache was really constrained
指定缓存确实受到限制
so you had to provide a name on the
因此您必须在
cache a notation that that was the only
缓存那是唯一的注释
way so you would do - every cache names
这样的方式-每个缓存名称
the name of the cache because it was the
缓存的名称，因为它是
only way to specify the attribute was
指定属性的唯一方法是
mandatory right so if you forget to
强制性权利，所以如果您忘记
specify it the annotation has no default
指定它注释没有默认值
value so you get a computation error and
值，因此您会得到计算错误，并且
when your code doesn't compile so it's
当您的代码无法编译时
easy for you to understand something was
你容易理解的东西是
wrong in the meantime the community said
同时，社区人士说错了
okay we would like more features we
好吧，我们想要更多功能，
would like to be able to export to
希望能够出口到
externalize that stuff we would be able
外部化我们可以做到的
to specify the cache names at the class
在类中指定缓存名称
level instead which is the cache config
级别，而是缓存配置
that you are that's commented out of the
你是那个被评论出来的
top so instead of repeating the name of
顶部，所以不必重复名称
the cache for every method you would put
您将放置的每种方法的缓存
it at class level and it will be applied
它在班级上将被应用
automatically for all the caches that we
自动为我们所有的缓存
use come let reduce copy paste and
使用来减少复制粘贴和
improvement ability does so it's really
改善能力确实如此
really a better problem now the
现在确实是一个更好的问题
attribute is no longer mandatory right
属性不再是强制性权利
because if you specify at the class
因为如果您在课堂上指定
level you don't need to specify that on
级别，您无需在
the meta level anymore
元级别了
so there is no compiler warning if
因此，如果没有编译器警告
you're in the sunny day cases with only
你在晴天的情况下
one method you just put at cache ever
您刚刚放入缓存的一种方法
you don't get any warning and you try to
您没有收到任何警告，然后尝试
start your app and spring framework
启动您的应用程序和spring框架
complains because it couldn't find the
抱怨，因为找不到
cache so that's a very very nice example
缓存，这是一个非常非常好的例子
in this plenty of them we're working
在很多这样的工作中
with the IDE teams helps actually are
与IDE团队的帮助实际上是
you to understand that stuff understand
你明白那些东西明白
history well you don't have to
历史，你不必
understand history that's the point you
了解历史就是你的重点
get a warning telling you hey there is
得到警告告诉你嘿
no cache names there are you sure that's
没有缓存名称，您确定是
what you want and if if one that's what
你想要什么，如果那是什么
you ended if you uncommon the one and
如果不寻常，你就结束了
class over the warning goes away exactly
上警告课完全消失
so there's another thing about a
所以关于
scheduler notation which I just enabled
我刚刚启用的调度程序符号
there's a condition attribute here and
这里有一个条件属性，
it looks funny because it has this the
它看起来很有趣，因为它具有
screen background here so that actually
屏幕背景在这里，以便实际上
hints me in my color setup color scheme
在我的配色方案中提示我
setup that this string is actually a
设置该字符串实际上是一个
springy L or spread expression so the
弹性L或散布的表情，因此
caching framework actually will evaluate
缓存框架实际上将评估
this condition at runtime to determine
此条件在运行时确定
if it's casual or not right and not only
无论是休闲还是不正确，不仅
do we see this highlighted in a special
我们会在特殊的地方看到这个吗
way but we also have full support for
方式，但我们也有全力支持
spell expressions because the IDE knows
拼写表达式，因为IDE知道
that this conditional attribute must be
该条件属性必须是
a spell expression so we inject to spell
咒语表达，所以我们注入咒语
language support in this place we have
在这个地方我们有语言支持
Auto completion syntax highlighting and
自动完成语法高亮显示和
I can even for example control click to
我什至可以控制点击
the corresponding resource parameter so
相应的资源参数
that something new in the latest version
最新版本中的新内容
we have now really context dependent
我们现在真的依赖于上下文
resolving for parameters on the method
解析方法的参数
level and any kind of implicit variables
级别和任何隐式变量
which are available in that specific
在该特定版本中可用
context so for example the caching
上下文，例如缓存
framework also adds some special
框架还添加了一些特殊的
variables here like the sketches
这里的变量像草图
collection and many many more the same
集合，还有很多相同的东西
is also true for spring security so let
对于弹簧安全性也是如此，所以让
me just show that very quickly when I
我只是很快地表现出来
have the spring security annotation here
在这里有spring安全注释
pre-authorized and again green
预授权，然后再次绿色
background and I get Auto completion for
后台，我得到自动完成
all the spring security methods which
所有的弹簧安全方法
are available because the IDE knows that
可用，因为IDE知道
they are bound automatically when you
它们会在您自动绑定
use spring security and this notation
使用spring安全性和这种表示法
and of course we can again control click
当然，我们可以再次控制点击
here
这里
we can show documentation on the method
我们可以显示该方法的文档
sorry wrong shortcut No
对不起，错误的快捷方式
yeah that so that's a very nice way to
是的，那是一个非常好的方法
work with spell and another thing we
使用咒语和另一件事
added for spell is we have no dedicated
为法术添加的是我们没有专用的
crawler settings for that language so
该语言的搜寻器设置，因此
when you go to your colors and fonts
当您使用颜色和字体时
scheme you will actually see a spring
方案，您实际上会看到春天
yell entry here and you can customize
在这里大喊条目，您可以自定义
all these attributes of the spell
咒语的所有这些属性
language to your likings so the special
您喜欢的语言，所以特别
support really is again is very
支持真的是非常非常
different from one feature to the other
与一个功能不同
for instance for the cache you can
例如对于缓存，您可以
inject the cache names the method name
注入缓存名称方法名称
the target instance you can inject
您可以注入的目标实例
parameters in a certain way if you look
参数以某种方式看
at spring security they have very
在春季安全，他们有非常
expressive spell expression support as
表达性咒语表达支持为
well and the context is different but
好，上下文不同，但是
because the ID knows about them you'll
因为ID知道他们，您会
get dedicated order completion for the
获得专用的订单完成
things you're trying to use and that
您尝试使用的东西
that's yet another story interesting
那是另一个有趣的故事
story if you if you go back to the cache
故事，如果您返回缓存
example and you show the Javadoc for the
示例，您将显示Javadoc
condition attribute you will see that
条件属性，您将看到
there is plenty of content there ok you
那里有很多内容，好的
can do this you can do that you can do
可以做到这一点，你可以做到的，你可以做到的
this and actually people complaining I'm
这实际上是人们在抱怨我
trying to use that condition thing and I
试图使用这种条件的东西，我
don't know what I can do with it can you
不知道我能用它做什么
please make sure that I have an
请确保我有一个
immediate access to that information it
立即访问该信息
turns out that well IntelliJ IDEA has
事实证明IntelliJ IDEA有
improved the support for that so instead
改进了对此的支持，所以改为
of reading all that that you just do the
阅读您所做的所有事情
usual roto completion command and you
通常的roto完成命令，您
see what you can use yeah so the root
看看你能用什么，所以根
object we just saw in a Java doc is
我们刚刚在Java文档中看到的对象是
available here again it knows the type
再次在这里可用，它知道类型
so we can navigate there and yeah I
所以我们可以在那里导航，是的，我
think that's very nice to have this kind
觉得有这种感觉很好
of very context-sensitive
非常上下文相关
support for Springheel it shows some
对Springheel的支持，表明了一些
stat about spring MVC now okay so spring
关于春季MVC的统计信息现在可以了，所以春季
MVC was traditionally configured with
传统上，MVC配置有
XML they also switch to an annotation
他们还将XML切换到注释
set up so I'm just going quickly to the
设置好后，我将快速进入
corresponding set up class which is
对应的设置类是
purely annotation based we support that
纯粹基于注释，我们支持
now finally so we actually scan this
现在终于，所以我们实际上扫描了
code
码
ode to understand what your setup is
颂歌了解您的设置是什么
about and we can see all of this also in
关于，我们也可以在这里看到所有这些
the spring framework facet so what we
春天框架的方面，所以我们
have here is an auto detected spring MVC
这里有一个自动检测到的弹簧MVC
context so we just scanned your whole
上下文，所以我们只是扫描了整个
project we found that spring MVC config
项目中我们发现spring MVC config
base class we inspect the code you've
基类，我们检查您拥有的代码
wrote there and we set up all of this
写在那里，我们建立了所有这一切
automatically for you and the nice thing
自动为您和美好的事物
is it also detects all the beans which
它是否也检测到所有的豆子
are related to spring MVC like viewers
与喜欢春季MVC的观众有关
all of us and stuff like that when you
我们所有人和类似的东西，当你
use any of the cause you have here for
将您在此处的任何原因用于
example to configure video resource and
配置视频资源的示例
you want just JSP or free market support
您只需要JSP或免费市场支持
of course you don't want choice B but
当然，您不希望选择B，但是
free mark or some other proper
免费商标或其他适当的商标
technology and it would actually set up
技术，它实际上会建立
all the stuff just for you so we have to
所有的东西都只为你，所以我们必须
view technologies here for demonstration
在此处查看技术进行演示
purposes and let's just quickly go to
目的，让我们快速进入
our controller by the way the spring
顺便说一下我们的控制器
tool window also has a dedicated tab for
工具窗口还具有专用的选项卡
spring MVC so when we go here we can see
春天的MVC，所以当我们去这里时，我们可以看到
the controller and the request mappings
控制器和请求映射
here again the presence of getter icon
这里再次出现吸气剂图标
on the left means okay spring knows am
在左边意味着春天知道
sorry IntelliJ IDE knows about that
抱歉，IntelliJ IDE知道这一点
stuff and can give you assistance so the
东西，可以给你帮助，所以
upper bound perform actually is
上限执行实际上是
old-school because we are using a JSP
老派，因为我们使用的是JSP
here and you get full auto completion
在这里，您将获得完全自动完成
here to reference that file I can
这里可以引用该文件
control click here go to the JSP page go
控制单击此处转到JSP页面转到
back to the controller we added an
回到控制器，我们添加了一个
attribute here to our model with the
将此处归因于我们的模型
name and attribute for JSP when we go to
转到时，JSP的名称和属性
the JSP page we can actually control
我们实际上可以控制的JSP页面
click and go back to the controller so
单击并返回到控制器，以便
IntelliJ understands all of this right
IntelliJ了解所有这些权利
so as you type as you as to start
这样当您键入开始时
putting up your model you will have full
建立您的模型，您将拥有完整的
auto completion
自动完成
in your views as well and the same thing
在您看来也是一样
works with free-market velocity now as
现在以自由市场的速度运作
well so when we go to the free-market
好吧，当我们去自由市场时
view we can also use this guitar icon
查看我们也可以使用此吉他图标
here or my favorite shortcut is actually
还是我最喜欢的快捷方式实际上是
navigate related symbol that's your
导航相关符号就是你的
second February okay yes okay all right
二月二号好吧好吧好吧
you already have one okay I'm rerunning
您已经可以了，我正在重新运行
in every couple of minutes but we latest
每隔几分钟，但我们最新
symbol what does it it expects the
象征它期望什么
current context it could be a file it
当前上下文可能是一个文件吗
could be some methods some some class
可能是某些类的某些方法
declaration and it tries to figure out
声明，它试图找出
what is this and what kind of other
这又是什么
files are related to this so when we are
文件与此相关，所以当我们
in our request mapping method it will
在我们的请求映射方法中
know that we are there and it will show
知道我们在那里，它将显示
me a list of matching stuff one of them
我列出了与之匹配的东西之一
is the view that is actually used in
是实际用于的视图
this request mapping and the other one
此请求映射和另一个
is actually the spring configuration
实际上是弹簧配置
that includes this controller class so
包括这个控制器类
that's a very nice way again to see who
这是再次查看谁的好方法
is working with this current element and
正在使用此当前元素，并且
here we have a free market view and we
在这里，我们有自由的市场观点，我们
have of course the same support free
当然有免费的相同支持
market velocity time leaf it's all there
市场速度时间叶就在那里
right out of the box
开箱即用
don't you have about that that actually
你真的没有那个吗
shows that that thing a button that
显示那个东西一个按钮
actually shows how that value was set
实际显示该值是如何设置的
yes again my favorite third favorite
是的，再次是我的最爱
shortcut the quick definition so I can
快捷方式快速定义，以便我可以
actually see the code that puts that
实际看到的代码
object in my model so you get basically
我模型中的对象，所以您基本上可以
the ID right you get a full link between
正确的ID，您将获得
your model and controller you can
您的模型和控制器，您可以
actually see in one way or the other how
实际上以一种或另一种方式看
it works
有用
it's intuitive because because of the
这很直观，因为
name of the view matches to a certain
视图名称与特定名称匹配
location you don't have to find in the
您不必在
file yourself you just click on the name
归档自己，只需单击名称
of the view and you and
的观点，你和
and okay said you know so the last
好吧，说你知道，所以最后
little thing I want to show this spring
我想在今年春天展示的小东西
MVC support is it's also included in
MVC支持也包含在其中
go-to symbol which allows you to go to
转到符号，使您可以转到
any kind of thing and the project it
任何事情和项目
could be a lot of things actually when I
实际上当我可能有很多事情
type a forward slash
输入正斜杠
it will also include my request methods
它还将包括我的请求方法
here so you can quickly go to any URI
在这里，您可以快速转到任何URI
which is defined in your spring MVC
在您的春季MVC中定义
project if you don't remember the name -
项目，如果您不记得名字-
controller class mapping for example
控制器类映射例如
that's a nice way to find the
这是找到
corresponding controller again create
相应的控制器再次创建
definition right there is a question
定义权有一个问题
there yep can you can you speak louder
是的，你能大声说吗
please
请
so the question was can you rename the
所以问题是您可以重命名
variable and would I pick it up yes no I
变量，我会把它捡起来是不是我
remember no it's broken for free market
记住不，它被自由市场打破了
works in JSP I have to fix it for free
在JSP中有效，我必须免费修复
market right so yeah in theory it works
市场权利，所以理论上是可行的
it will work for the next release okay
它将适用于下一个版本
okay so much about spring MVC we just
好吧，关于Spring MVC，我们只是
touch the upper stuff there's much more
触摸高级东西还有更多
let's go to our favorite spring project
让我们去我们最喜欢的春季项目
spring boot of course so I guess most of
当然是春季靴子，所以我猜大部分
you are aware spring boot we have a
您知道春季靴子有一个
dedicated project wizard here the spring
春天的专用项目向导
initializer which basically mimics what
初始化器，基本上模仿什么
you can do on these starts bring our own
您可以在这些开始中带来我们自己的
website and it's actually using status
网站，它实际上是在使用状态
window dial by the way so whenever we
顺便说一下窗口拨号
push some changes to start of spring
推动一些变化以开始春天
delay or new dependencies new settings
延迟或新的依赖项新设置
the ID actually contact the server to
该ID实际上与服务器联系以
download the metadata so it's it's
下载元数据就可以了
updated automatically with that stuff
用那个东西自动更新
right so we are going through this very
对，所以我们正在经历
quickly I'm just picking the defaults
很快我就选择了默认值
and here we can select the spring boot
在这里我们可以选择弹簧靴
version we have a long list of spring
版本我们有很多春季
starters which are available here
在这里可用的起动器
because they're hard to find we
因为他们很难找到我们
implemented some search and filtering so
实施了一些搜索和过滤，因此
it will not only search in a name but
它不仅会搜索名称，还会搜索
also in the description and I like them
也在说明中，我喜欢他们
for you we are just going to pick the
为您，我们将选择
web dependency and but one thing is
网络依赖，但有一件事是
funny when I go back to an old version
当我回到旧版本时很有趣
of springboard some of them are disabled
跳板中的一些被禁用
and the reason is that some stars are
原因是有些星星
only available in a range of spring boot
仅在一系列弹簧靴中可用
versions and if you use the tooltip here
版本以及您是否在此处使用工具提示
you can actually see what the
您实际上可以看到
requirements are okay so let's use a
要求还可以，所以我们使用
more modern version so that's really
更现代的版本，所以这真的
you're getting started experience with
您正在开始使用
IntelliJ IDEA in Springwood right you do
Springwood的IntelliJ IDEA对吗
create new project you go through the
创建新项目，您需要
wizard and then you get a project that's
向导，然后您得到一个
ready to use remember what we've taught
准备使用请记住我们所教的内容
about the spring facet if you use spring
关于弹簧面（如果使用弹簧）
boot don't worry about that
开机不用担心
it's detected automatically for you yeah
它会自动为您检测
so what I did was to contact the start
所以我要做的就是联系开始
spring our website create a project for
春天我们的网站创建一个项目
you on the server returns zip unpack it
您在服务器上返回的zip解压缩它
for you set up the IntelliJ project and
为您设置IntelliJ项目并
create a spring facet Springwood
创建一个弹簧面Springwood
contacts auto-configuration
联系人自动配置
already triggered we are ready to go and
已经触发，我们准备出发了
there is also a run configuration for
还有一个运行配置
the app that's being created at
在以下位置创建的应用
immediately so all you can do really is
立即，所以您真正能做的就是
press run and yeah be starting so I can
按运行，是的开始，所以我可以
just hit run application it will build
只需点击运行它将构建的应用程序
and my spring boot application which
和我的spring boot应用程序
does nothing right now will start so
现在什么也不做，所以会开始
spring wood is nice when you understand
当你了解春天的木材就很好了
what Auto configuration is about writers
什么是自动配置的作家
that's the key the magic behind it yeah
这是它背后的魔力的关键
I don't like the magic word that yeah
我不喜欢那个神奇的词
you get the idea so you you probably
你有主意，所以你可能
know by now that spring boot as this
现在知道春季靴子是这样的
Auto configuration concept so whenever
自动配置的概念，因此无论何时
you put is something in your class class
你在课堂上放的东西
like we we've seen that yeah
就像我们看到的那样
added the web starter that's going to
添加了将要使用的网络启动器
bring spring MVC tomcat embedded and
将Spring MVC tomcat嵌入并
jackson and well basically the basic
杰克逊，基本上基本上
stuff you need to build a web
建立网站所需的东西
application spring boot will detect that
应用程序Spring Boot将检测到
and because you have no configuration it
而且因为您没有配置
will do something by default there's a
默认情况下会做某事
bunch of other configuration and it
一堆其他配置和它
would be nice if you could have a way to
如果您有办法可以
actually know what's going on so the
实际上知道发生了什么，所以
JetBrains team is actually working on
JetBrains团队实际上正在研究
that and we can see some of the stuff
那我们可以看到一些东西
they already done so again this is our
他们已经这样做了，这是我们的
spring convict model graph it shows
显示的春季定罪模型图
nothing special right we have only our
没有什么特别的权利，我们只有我们的
demo application main class annotated
演示应用程序主类已注释
with the springboard application class
与跳板应用程序类
so where's all the auto convicts they
所以他们所有的汽车定罪者在哪里
are provided by spring boot themselves
由弹簧靴本身提供
so there's a switch up here to enable
所以这里有一个开关可以启用
library nodes and when I fix the display
库节点以及修复显示时
you can see all the auto configuration
您可以看到所有自动配置
which is actually
实际上是
triggered automatically by using
通过使用自动触发
springboard and you can inspect is this
跳板，你可以检查一下
what I actually want right so that's a
我真正想要的就是一个
nice way to see what Auto configuration
查看自动配置的好方法
is kicking in if everything is set up
如果一切都设置好了
correctly and again we can navigate to
正确地，我们可以再次导航到
any of those nodes and see any kind of
这些节点中的任何一个，并看到任何一种
problems here and think it's thinking
问题在这里，以为是在想
this way you've seen the relationship
这样你就看到了关系
with auto wiring so we've defined a
具有自动接线功能，因此我们定义了一个
being of type long that's a bad example
类型长，这是一个不好的例子
but okay and then we had this gutter
但是好吧，然后我们有了这个装订线
icon saying okay yes this being has been
图标说可以，是的，
Auto wired and if you click on it you
自动连线，如果您单击它
can jump to the definition right with
可以直接跳到定义
the auto configuration let's say you
自动配置，假设您
rely on the you're using JDBC template
依靠您正在使用的JDBC模板
whatever reason or JMS template what not
出于什么原因或JMS模板什么都没有
and you inject that in your component
然后将其注入您的组件中
but that's Auto configure by spring boot
但这是通过Spring Boot自动配置的
so it's not there yet because it's very
所以它还不存在，因为它非常
very hard to do but you can think of
很难做到，但你可以想到
maybe maybe we hope in future release
也许我们希望将来发布
having that kind of feature photo
有那种特色照片
configuration so you know that for
配置，所以您知道
instance if you get a warning and it
实例，如果您收到警告，
already works for quite a lot of things
已经适用于很多事情
basically IntelliJ IDEA doesn't know
基本上IntelliJ IDEA不知道
about that stuff
关于那个东西
maybe that's because something in your
也许是因为你的东西
configuration on your on your class pass
在您的课程通行证上进行配置
isn't right maybe you forgot to add I
不对，也许你忘了加我
don't know the right starter or
不知道正确的启动器或
something like that so talking about
像这样的事情
starters there there are many
起动器有很多
annotations following a certain name
带有特定名称的注释
pattern they all start with enable and
模式都以enable和
then something so I might actually want
那是我可能真正想要的
some WebSocket support so I think
一些WebSocket支持，所以我认为
there's an annotation for that enable
有一个启用注释
web socket which is not on our class bus
Web套接字不在我们的类总线上
right now so we get an error but antenna
现在，我们得到一个错误，但天线
is actually clever enough to figure out
实际上足够聪明以找出
the corresponding starter for commonly
通常的相应启动器
used annotations or classes so I can
使用了注释或类，所以我可以
again he'll tall old enter my definite
他又高大了，进入我的确定
first high priority shortcut and it will
第一个高优先级快捷方式，它将
actually pick the WebSocket starter for
实际选择WebSocket启动器
me and when we go to our pom mixin L we
我，当我们去pom mixin L时，
will see that it was just added
会看到它刚刚被添加
automatically for us right it's the same
对我们来说自动是一样的
thing right a community feedback
正确的事，社区反馈
feedback loop
反馈回路
if you have an annotation that you you
如果您有注释
think you might be useful to add dental
认为您添加牙齿可能会有用
guys I'm adding annotation foo it should
伙计们，我要添加注释foo，应该
add starter bar and it was the class
添加启动栏，这是班
it's very easy for them to add that so
他们很容易添加
do not hesitate to get in touch with
不要犹豫与
them right so with all this Auto
他们正确，所以所有这些自动
configuration how can you actually
配置你怎么能实际
configure it right it's just some blank
正确配置它只是空白
board yeah
是的
so you've seen probably at the at the
所以您可能已经在
keynote at some point what I've done
在某些时候的主题演讲
again in the keynote I can't remember oh
再次在主题演讲中，我不记得了哦
yeah
是的
the location of the weather so there was
天气的位置，所以有
do that weather locations hard-coded I
将天气位置硬编码吗
move that to a given class and all the
将其移动到给定的类和所有
sudden some auto-completion magic
突然出现一些自动完成的魔法
appeared so what we want to do now is to
出现了，所以我们现在要做的是
show you our intelligence you building
向您展示我们建立的智慧
that infrastructure so what we see here
基础设施，所以我们在这里看到的
in the application properties file works
在应用程序属性文件中工作
a similar way and Yama files are all the
以类似的方式，Yama文件都是
configuration keys which are exposed by
公开的配置密钥
these starters we have available here
这些启动器，我们在这里可用
and yeah maybe we want to add some own
是的，也许我们想添加一些自己的
configurations so so the way it works
配置，使其工作方式
with Springwood is you create a POJO
与Springwood一起创建POJO吗
that defines your configuration
定义您的配置
structure and you use the configuration
结构，然后使用配置
properties and notation to give a prefix
属性和表示法以提供前缀
for your keys so you basically have a
为您的钥匙，所以你基本上有一个
POJO that's going to be buying from from
POJO将从以下位置购买
the environment so in this case I'm
环境，在这种情况下，我是
going to say I want to bind that object
要说我想绑定那个对象
to the spring one prefix so every key
弹簧一个前缀，所以每个键
starting with spring one spring one dot
从春天开始一春天一点
something will be bound to that object
某些东西将绑定到该对象
so in this case I have spring spring one
所以在这种情况下，我有一个弹簧
dot my property if you specify that in
点我的财产，如果您在
config it's going to call the setter
配置它将调用设置器
right there but we can see we have a red
就在那里，但我们可以看到我们有一个红色
thing telling us that something might be
东西告诉我们可能是
wrong some annotation processor is
错误的一些注释处理器是
missing so maybe we can click on that
缺少，所以也许我们可以单击
link and see what happens
链接，看看会发生什么
you can read the duck it will explain
你可以读鸭会解释
you in more details what I'm going to
您会更详细地了解我要做什么
say so basically for
基本上是这样说的
the content assistance to work the idea
内容协助以实现想法
needs to know about your keys and the
需要了解您的钥匙和
way it knows about your keys is via a
它知道您的钥匙的方式是通过
metadata file so it's a file that's
元数据文件，因此它是
built that generated at runtime looking
建立在运行时生成的外观
at your code so yan is adding the
在您的代码上，所以yan正在添加
necessary to the project right now it's
现在该项目所必需的
really a single dependency you don't use
确实是您不使用的单个依赖项
that at runtime it's only used at a
在运行时仅用于
computation time that's why there is the
计算时间，这就是为什么
optional flag on it and if you compile
可选标志，如果您进行编译
and you go back to the configuration you
然后回到配置
should see the the things being
应该看到的东西
available not not yet right oh we forgot
尚不可用，哦，我们忘了
one thing sorry we forgot something -
对不起，我们忘记了一件事-
forgot to say that we want to enable
忘了说我们要启用
that stuff no deafness in the area so we
那个地方没有耳聋，所以我们
need actually to go back to our
实际上需要回到我们的
configuration class and one thing we
配置类和一件事，我们
need to tell spring boot is that we
需要告诉春天的靴子是，我们
actually want to enable support for this
确实想为此提供支持
by listing the corresponding
通过列出相应的
configuration classes we want to have
我们想要的配置类
here I'm sorry this person wrong file so
在这里我很抱歉这个人错误的文件，所以
we are going to don't do the application
我们将不做申请
right that you're doing that on yourself
正确的是您正在自己做
that's bad so now it also shows up a
不好，所以现在它也显示了
spring beam because again the IDE
弹簧梁，因为再次是IDE
understands that this is now used by
了解到现在，
spring wood implicitly we are going to
隐性地，我们要
rebuild everything and I think now it
重建一切，我现在想
should work right
应该工作正常
there it is so now we can configure our
就是这样，现在我们可以配置我们的
property we can control click here to go
我们可以控制的属性，请点击此处
to the beam you also have this gutter a
到光束，你也有这个排水沟
con that's my favorite one
缺点，这是我最喜欢的一个
so the gutter I can illegally get X to
所以我可以非法将X装到天沟
the setter yeah it allows an inverse
二传手是的，它允许逆
search so I can actually see usages of
搜索，以便我实际上可以看到
that property in my configuration files
我的配置文件中的那个属性
right so you can immediately spot what
对，所以您可以立即发现
properties are actually used in your
属性实际上是在您的
config and which ones are exposed but
配置和哪些暴露，但
not yet overwritten or configured so
尚未覆盖或配置为
that's a nice way to do this you also
这也是一个很好的方法
add that in Thein usage and if you
将其添加到Thein用法中，如果您
rename the property it would
重命名该属性
automatically rename that in config so
自动在配置中重命名，以便
you get the refactoring options working
您可以使用重构选项
so right now we have a string property
所以现在我们有一个字符串属性
which is a bit aggressive stupid because
这有点激进的愚蠢，因为
springboard and IntelliJ cannot tell
跳板和IntelliJ无法分辨
anything about possibly values which are
关于可能的值是什么
allowed for this property or anything
允许使用此属性或其他任何东西
else so what we need to do here is to
否则，我们在这里要做的是
add a fire so this is really an advanced
加火，所以这真的是一个高级
it's really an advanced setup right so
这真的是一个高级设置，所以
what we want to show you is if you want
我们想告诉你的是，如果你想
to provide even better assistance for
为...提供更好的帮助
your users you have a key it has a
您的用户，您拥有一把钥匙
certain value and you want to direct
一定的价值，你想直接
them to what kind of values can be used
他们以什么样的价值观可以使用
the way you would do that is probably in
你可能会这样做
this particular case is to use an engine
这种特殊情况是使用引擎
and a new type and the ID will
并使用新的类型和ID
automatically extract the values and
自动提取值并
provide it to completion for the values
提供完整的值
but let's say for some reason you can't
但由于某些原因，您不能
and well it needs to be a string
而且它需要是一个字符串
whatever reason and you still want to
不管什么原因，你仍然想
have a to completion
完成
Springwood has defined additional
Springwood定义了其他
metadata that you can write to provide
您可以编写以提供的元数据
to provide additional basically
提供额外的基本
additional hints to that property and
该属性的其他提示，以及
you'll see also that you get auto
您还会看到自动
completion in the JSON file so if you
在JSON文件中完成，因此，如果您
don't know what you have to write you
不知道你要写什么
just ask the idea
只是问这个主意
I peel right so we will actually provide
我剥皮了，所以我们实际上会提供
a couple of valid values here I'm just
我只是几个有效值
giving them very stupid names and like
给他们起非常愚蠢的名字
that's individual object nihilistic
那是虚无的个体对象
writer so I need to add this here right
作家，所以我需要在这里添加它
there is a comma missing
缺少逗号
and when we rerun the annotation
当我们重新运行注释时
processor it will pick up those hints
处理器，它将接收那些提示
for us and expose them here so oh
为了我们，把它们暴露在这里哦
there's an error in the design I think I
我认为我的设计有错误
don't see I don't see either wait now
没有看到我也没有等待
that's good okay we get it try again you
很好，我们知道了，再试一次
know sometimes it is a bit picky with
知道有时候有点挑剔
picking up changes so a full rebuild
接受更改，以便全面重建
sometimes helps here yes now we have it
有时在这里有帮助，现在我们有了
so now the annotation processor process
所以现在注释处理器过程
all this additional metadata we just
所有这些额外的元数据
provided for our property and we can for
提供给我们的财产，我们可以
example define a list of valid values we
这个例子定义了一个有效值列表
can define class name which should be
可以定义应该是的类名
specified local names stuff vectors so
指定本地名称的东西矢量
that is quite impressive number of stuff
数量可观
here there is a really rich model so
这里有一个非常丰富的模型，所以
this you'll see that when you use spring
这会在您使用弹簧时看到
boot so when you use spring boot with
引导，因此当您使用spring boot与
IntelliJ IDE and you see that rich order
IntelliJ IDE，您会看到丰富的订单
completion for values keep in mind it's
记住价值的完成是
very easy to add that to your own key
轻松将其添加到您自己的密钥中
right but what if I want to change that
是的，但是如果我要更改该怎么办
value of only when I run the application
仅当我运行应用程序时的值
in a certain state right we can do this
在某种状态下，我们可以做到这一点
actually in the run configuration so
实际上在运行配置中
there's a dedicated run configuration
有专门的运行配置
type for spring boot applications here
此处用于春季靴子应用
and we already see this section here for
我们已经在这里看到此部分
spring boot specific sections Josh
春季靴特定款式Josh
really hates me for hiding the banner
真的讨厌我隐藏横幅
but I'm fine with that
但是我很好
and one possibility we added here is -
我们在这里添加的一种可能性是-
all right parameters not in the
好的参数不在
configuration files but also in the run
配置文件也可以在运行中
configuration so I can add additional
配置，所以我可以添加其他
parameters again use code completion
参数再次使用代码完成
here so maybe I want to redefine my
在这里所以也许我想重新定义我的
spring one property stuff
春季一物产
and again we get completion for the
再次，我们完成了
values here again and it what it will do
值再次在这里，它会做什么
I specified value to in my default
我将默认值指定为
application properties but when I run it
应用程序属性，但是当我运行它时
from within the IDE I want actually to
从我实际上想在IDE中
override this parameter and I can just
覆盖此参数，我可以
do this in the run configuration without
在运行配置中执行此操作而无需
touching any of the config files without
触摸任何配置文件而无需
using some sophisticated stuff which I
用一些我会用的东西
might use a better angle I know that
可能会使用更好的角度，我知道
that's very nice and accessible to
很好，可以访问
change stuff on the fly just for testing
快速更改内容以进行测试
out stuff and yeah that's it and we're
是的东西，是的，我们
running out of time and afraid yeah so
时间不多了，害怕，所以
maybe one or two questions left yes
也许还剩下一两个问题
please
请
yeah so the question was if you have a
是的，问题是您是否有
lot of custom properties can you share
您可以分享很多自定义属性
them wire jars for example between
他们之间例如铁丝罐
different microservices oh yeah the
不同的微服务哦，是的
scope is really the the project really
范围确实是项目
so if you have the you have the pojo in
所以如果你有，你就拥有pojo
a certain project you add the annotation
在某个项目中添加注释
processor it will automatically include
处理器，它将自动包括
the metadata in the jar and whenever the
罐子中的元数据以及
joist on the class pass it will work and
班级通行证上的托梁将起作用，并且
you can have as many as you want so the
您可以根据需要拥有任意数量，因此
idea would actually reconciliate all
这个想法实际上会调和所有人
those files and provide you are unified
这些文件，并为您提供统一
repository for the keys that's already
已经存在的密钥的存储库
what we have in Springwood if you look
如果您看，我们在斯普林伍德有什么
at Springwood certain modules actually
在Springwood实际上某些模块
ship with metadata we don't have one
附带元数据，我们没有一个
giantic file with everything it's
巨型文件及其所有内容
already isolated more questions or you
已经隔离了更多问题，或者您
can come and we can have a chat thank
可以来，我们可以聊天谢谢
you very much ok thank you very much
你非常好，非常感谢你